- Yah!
- Oh. yeah!
Michelangelo is on the move!
Heeyah!
You don't know what to do.
I'm here. I'm there.
I could be anywhere.
How do you stop
what you can't even see?
Like that?
Good one. Leo.
All right. Donnie.
Put down the staff
and no one gets hurt.
Uh. you said that last time.
Raph. and then you hurt me.
Yeah. but less
than I would have.
Yeah. right.
Wah!
Ah!
Yah!
Should've dropped the staff?
Should've dropped the staff.
Okay. okay. Ow!
I'm down!
Onegai shimasu.
Whatever you say.
Ah!
Agh!
Nice try.
Ya me!
You all did very well.
But I did better.
This is about
self-improvement. Raphael.
It is not about winning
and losing.
I know. sensei.
But I won and they lost.
Ah. ah. ah!
But what's really important
is that we all did our best.
Good job. everyone!
Ah.
♪ Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles ♪
♪ Heroes in a half shell.
turtle power ♪
♪ Here we go.
it's a lean. green. ninja team ♪
♪ On the scene.
cool teens doing ninja things ♪
♪ So extreme.
out the sewers like laser beams ♪
♪ Get rocked with
the shell shocked pizza kings ♪
♪ Can't stop
these radical dudes ♪
♪ The secret of the ooze
made the chosen few ♪
♪ Emerge from the shadows
to make their move ♪
♪ The good guys win
and the bad guys lose ♪
♪ Leonardo's the leader
in blue ♪
♪ Does anything it takes
to get his ninjas through ♪
♪ Donatello is a fellow.
has a way with machines ♪
♪ Raphael's got the most
attitude on the team ♪
♪ Michelangelo.
he's one of a kind ♪
♪ And you know just where to
find him when it's party time ♪
♪ Master splinter taught 'em
every single skill they need ♪
♪ To be one lean.
mean. green incredible team ♪
♪ Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles ♪
♪ Heroes in a half shell.
turtle power ♪
Mm.
Bleh!
There's a little more
algae and worms left
if anyone wants it.
Anybody?
- No. thanks.
- I'm good.
All yours.
Well. I guess no one
left room for... Cake!
- Whoa!
- It is a cake!
Made of... algae...
and... worms.
What's the frosting
made out of?
You don't wanna know.
Happy Mutation day!
Ah. yes.
15 years ago today.
our lives changed forever
and we became the unlikeliest
of families.
Tell us the story.
Master Splinter.
Michelangelo. I have already
told it many times.
Please!
Pleeeease!
Please. It's the only way
to shut Mikey up.
Ah. very well.
Many years ago.
when I was still human.
I was leaving the pet store
with four baby turtles.
- That was us?
- Yes.
Don't interrupt!
I passed a strange man
on the street.
Something felt off about him.
I decided to follow.
Go no further.
This place is a place
where you are not allowed
to be in this place.
We have been seen
in this place by you.
so this is not a place
that will be left by you.
That was the beginning
of our life together.
It was the mysterious substance
in this canister
that. in a way.
gave birth to us all.
Mom.
So. sensei. now that we're 15.
I think we're finally ready to
go up to the surface. don't you?
Yes.
And no.
- Oh. man. come on.
- Lame.
I hate when he does that.
You have grown powerful.
but you are still young.
You lack the maturity
to use your skills wisely.
So. sensei. isn't that just no?
Yes...
And no.
Wisdom comes from experience.
And experience comes from
making mistakes.
Aha!
So in order for us
to gain the wisdom.
we have to make the mistakes.
- So we can go.
- No.
- And yes?
- No!
Oh!
Sensei. we know you're trying
to protect us.
but we can't spend our
whole lives hiding down here.
Mm.
You may go tonight.
High three!
Mr. Crenshaw.
status report!
Status?
I'll give you the status!
We're gonna blow up
in two seconds!
Thank you. captain.
Gentlemen. I have a bold
and daring plan.
There's no time for hesitation.
My orders must be carried out
without question!
Aye. sir!
You know this show
is stupid. right?
Space Heroes is a great show.
And captain Ryan
is a great hero.
Someday. I am gonna be
just like him.
Well. you do like
to hear yourself talk.
so you're on your way.
It's go time!
You are going up
to a strange and hostile world.
You must maintain awareness
at all times.
Aye. sensei!
- Stay in the shadows.
- Aye. sensei!
- Don't talk to strangers.
- Everyone is a stranger.
- Aye. sensei!
Make sure you go
before you leave.
The restrooms up there
are filthy.
Sensei!
Good luck. my sons.
- I am so pumped!
- Surface time!
Oh. this is gonna be epic!
Look both ways
before crossing the street!
It's so beautiful.
The city is just full
of possibility.
There could be an adventure
around this corner...
Or... or this one...
Or this one!
There's not.
but there could be!
Look at all the computers!
Is that the next
generation cadmium processor
with quantum encryption?
I don't know. Donatello.
Is it?
- It is!
- Guys. guys!
Check this out.
A hand made out of light.
Now it's an eye
made out of light.
And the hand again!
Now the eye's back!
Now the hand!
- Come on. genius.
- The eye!
So where to next?
Huh?
Ah!
That was kinda fun.
We're too exposed out here.
Come on.
Pizza.
Should we open it?
Careful!
It could be dangerous.
I think it's food.
It's not like any food
I ever saw.
I'll try it.
Mm! Mm.
Uh. yuck.
You guys won't like it.
I'll take the rest.
- No way!
- Nuh-uh!
Back off!
I never thought I'd taste
anything better
than worms and algae.
but this is amazing!
Right?
I love it up here!
Yeah-ha!
Whoohoo!
Ha. ha-ha!
Yippy!
Ha ha!
All right. guys.
it's getting late.
We should probably
head back home.
Lame.
Guys!
Look at that!
She's the most beautiful girl
I've ever seen.
Isn't she the only girl
you've ever seen?
My point still stands.
What?
What is this?
We gotta save 'em!
Splinter's instructions
were very clear.
We're supposed to stay away
from people.
And bathrooms.
I thought you wanted
to be a hero.
Since when do heroes
ask for permission?
They don't.
But...
Well. I'm going!
Help!
Hey!
Still standing. huh?
I'll fix that.
- Wah!
- Oh!
- Watch it!
- You watch it!
Watch it. Donnie!
Hyah!
What the...
Ah!
Oh. come on!
Ooh!
Oh! Ow!
Ha.
Hey. cut it out!
Stop! Ow!
Huh?
Agh!
Gotcha!
Aghh!
No. no. no. No.
Don't worry.
We're the good guys.
It's okay.
Whoops!
Sorry.
Watch out!
Huh?
They're getting away!
They got the girl!
You just jabbed me
with your sword.
Well. I didn't know you were
gonna land where I was stabbing.
You think you're tough. huh?
You think you're tough enough
to stand up
to my hot nunchuck fury?
Hyah!
Wah!
Huh?
I see.
Well. then...
Aah!
Stay back!
What the...
That is all kinds of wrong.
Aah!
Guys! Guys!
You're never gonna believe this!
That dude. he... he...
Had a brain!
We all have brains. Mikey.
Not all of us.
In our chests?
No. Mikey.
Not in our chests.
You're not listening to me!
Did you just slap me?
I was calming you down.
Why would that calm me down?
I think he's delusional.
Just-just... come here.
I'm telling you.
The big guy was a robot
and he had a freaky-weird alien
brain thing in his chest.
You gotta believe me.
- I'm not sure we do.
- Oh. yeah?
Well. you'll change your tune
when you see that he's...
Gone?
And so your inability
to work together
allowed them all to get away.
Well. maybe if I didn't have
to waste time
arguing with hero boy.
I could've saved them.
Hey. if you hadn't gotten
in my way.
I could have done it.
And you went flying off
on your own.
How smart was that?
Well. it would've
worked out great
if somebody hadn't hit me
in the head
with their nunchucks!
Well. none of this
would've happened if...
Somebody hadn't trusted us to go
up there in the first place.
Oh. geez.
Sensei. I didn't mean to...
- No. Michelangelo.
- You are right.
- I am?
- He is?
You were not fully prepared
for what was up there.
I trained you
to fight as individuals.
not as a team.
And as your teacher.
your father.
the responsibility for that
is mine.
Perhaps in another year
we can try again.
Another year?
Ha! Has everybody forgotten
that people were kidnapped?
They don't have a year!
sensei. we have
to do something now!
You weren't there. sensei.
You didn't see the way
that girl looked into my eyes.
She was scared.
And she was counting on me...
us... to save her!
Yes. you must save her.
I agree. sensei.
But in that fight.
we weren't exactly
a well-oiled machine.
Like that robot
with the brain thingy.
Give a rest!
Hmm.
If you are to fight
more effectively as a unit.
you are going to need a leader.
Can I be the leader?
Why should you be the leader?
I kicked your butt.
I should be the leader.
Hey. I'm smarter
than all you guys put together.
- It should be me.
- No way!
It should be me!
I don't really have a reason.
I just think it would be neat.
This is a difficult decision.
I will meditate on it.
It's Leonardo.
No hard feelings. Raph?
Stick it in your shell.
Explain to me one more time
what we're doing here.
Mikey. we've been over this.
That building has the same logo
as the van that was used
to kidnap the family.
So if we wait here long enough.
one of the kidnappers
will eventually show his face.
And when he does.
we'll make him tell us
where they took them.
And then we
got ourselves a van!
Just hit the guy I tell you to.
Will do!
Are you sure
this is gonna work?
Trust me.
They'll be here any second.
Oh!
Okay. I'm thinking
of something green.
Ga-reen.
Is it Raphael again?
Man. you're good at this!
Give it up already.
The guy's not gonna show.
We have to be patient.
No. you have to come up
with a better plan.
'cause the four of us
standing here
with our thumbs up our noses...
I don't think they'd fit.
Is pointless.
You sure about that. Raph?
He just showed up. didn't he?
I should've complained
two hours ago.
Gentlemen. I have a bold
and daring plan.
There's no time for hesitation.
My orders must be carried out
without question.
Guys?
Guys. wait up!
All right. buddy.
We can do this the easy way.
or... my vote... the hard way.
Yeah. look at it logically.
There are four of us
and one of you.
What are you gonna do?
- Yow!
- Whoa!
You had to ask!
- He's getting away again!
- No. he's not.
Whoa!
Ugh.
Now we're getting somewhere.
I don't know what that means.
Go around back.
Why didn't he just say so?
Huh?
Mom?
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player